Previously, on AMC's, "The Walking Dead."
《行尸走肉》前情提要
A single bullet ain't gonna do it.
一颗子弹解决不了任何问题
Make me a bullet.
给我做一颗子弹
Somebody has to pay the price.
有人会付出代价的
What is this?
这是什么
This little bad boy made from scratch.
这玩意是手工做出来的吗
You tell me who made this.
告诉我是谁做的
Please. Please don't.
求求你  不要
Please, god, no.
天啊  不要
I hate this. Please!
我讨厌这样  求你了
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8
原创翻译  双语字幕
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
最新连载海外影视剧下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com 仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
Welcome home, haircut.
欢迎回家  长毛
There's more at the library.
图书馆还有更多的书
A lot more.
多得多
You, uh...
你们
You have a library?
你们有图书馆吗
Your friend Daryl
你朋友达里尔
didn't get a chance to see it before he bounced.
离开之前没机会看到
He escaped?
他逃跑了吗
Yeah.
是的
You know where he is?
你知道他在哪吗
No.
不知道
I'd tell you if I did.
如果我知道  我会告诉你的
Vonda N. Mcintyre.
《旺达・N・ 麦金太尔》
Th-this will be satisfactory.
这本就行了
You hungry?
你饿了吗
I'll get you something. What do you want?
我给你弄点吃的  你想要什么
What do I want?
我想要什么
Yeah, to eat. What do you want?
是啊  吃什么  你想要什么
Anything?
什么都可以吗
Sure. Whatever.
是啊  随便
Really? Anything I want?
真的吗  我想要什么都行
Dude, yes.
哥们  是的
You can have anything. What do you want?
想吃什么都行  你想吃什么
- Can I have lobster? - No, you can't have lobster.
-我能吃龙虾吗  -不行
What the hell do you think this is?
你他妈以为这是什么地方
Do you have canned pasta and tomato sauce?
有罐头意面和番茄酱吗
You want orange-y or red?
你想要橙色的还是红色的
Orange-y.
橙色的
All right.
好
What about pickles? I-I like pickles.
有腌黄瓜吗  我爱吃腌黄瓜
We're out of pickles.
我们没腌黄瓜了
What about potato chips?
那薯片呢
We got chips.
我们有薯片
Number 42 makes them.
42号做的
Number 42 is a coding system for persons here?
42号是这里人的代码系统吗
For the workers, yeah.
是工人的
They make said chips fresh?
他们做的是新鲜薯片吗
Yeah, they got a kettle --
是啊  他们有个壶
No, thanks.
不用了  谢谢
Okay. I'll be back in 10.
好  我十分钟后回来
Enjoy your new place.
享受你的新地方吧
Good mornin', sunshine.
早上好  小子
Is it just as cozy as you remember?
这和你回忆中的一样舒适吗
You spent a lot of time on the wrong side of the door
你跟你妻子和蒂娜去愚蠢的自驾游之后
after that stupid road trip with the wife and Tina.
就花了许多时间待在门的错误一边
So let's talk about now.
我们现在谈谈吧
We went out looking for your little failed project
我们在边界周围花了几个小时
for a few hours, just around the perimeter --
寻找你的失败项目
Tip to taint, as it were --
从头到尾找了一遍
right about the time I had you thrown in here,
就在我让人把你扔进这里的时候
and when I got back,
我回来后
I realized I...
意识到自己
was short...
少了个
a wife.
妻子
Which one?
哪个
Sherry.
雪莉
You know anything about that, Dwighty boy?
你知道些什么吗  小德
'cause I got to tell you,
因为我得告诉你
that is one hell of a coincidence,
这真他妈太巧了
her leaving just a few short hours after Daryl took off.
达里尔走后几小时  她就离开了
Oh, and he didn't force his way out.
他根本没有靠武力打出去
No.
没有
Somebody opened the door for him.
有人为他开门了
It wasn't Sherry.
不是雪莉
Dwighty boy...
小德
Was it you?
是你吗
Did it work the other way around?
事情往反方向发展了吗
You were supposed to break him.
你本该击溃他的
Did he break you?
他把你感化了吗
I mean, let's face it --
实话实说
You've got some pretty legitimate grievances.
你有一些合理的不满
You change your stripes on me, Dwighty?
你背叛我了吗  德怀特
You startin' to see things different?
你开始有不同的想法了吗
After all this...
经历了这么多
Before and after...
之前和之后
Hell, after everything...
该死  经历了这么多之后
...Who are you, Dwight?
你到底是谁  德怀特
I'm Negan.
我是尼根
Daryl isn't like you.
达里尔和你不一样
He's...
他
Emotional.
有感情
So he's either on his way home,
所以他要么在回家的路上
Or he's coming back here
要么在回这里的路上
to try to kill some more of us.
试图多杀我们几个人
Mostly you and me.
主要是杀你和我
Either way, we'll find him.
无论怎样  我们都会找到他
So...
所以...
do you think you know where Sherry went?
你知道雪莉去哪了吗
Yeah.
知道
Bring her back.
把她带回来
Sort it out.
解决这事
Stitch him up.
给他缝缝针
Fix what you can fix.
把能治的地方都治一治
You don't think she did it?
你不认为是她做的吗
You think she did?
你觉得是她做的吗
I got to know her a little bit.
我对她有些了解
Not well.
虽然不是很了解
Well enough to know what happened.
但足以想明白是怎么回事了
She saw Daryl in here, in the state he was in.
她看见达里尔当时的处境
She let him go.
就把他放走了
She was soft.
她心软
She has a big heart.
很善良
You were just beaten and thrown in a cell --
你被打了一顿扔进牢里...
unfairly, if you ask me.
要我说的话很冤
And you're back to it.
而你跟没事人似的
You may wind up running an outpost for him.
说不定你以后会为他掌管一个哨站
You get it.
你懂的
I like to think that I do.
我觉得我也懂
The type of selfless, tender soul
那种无私  温柔
who would marry Negan to save her husband's life?
愿意嫁给尼根以救自己丈夫一命的人
That's exactly the kind of person who really isn't...
也正是不应该...
expected to be around anymore.
活到现在的人
Thanks.
谢了
Just trying to help.
只是想帮帮忙而已
Stuff people grow, stuff people make,
这里有大家种植的  制造的
stuff, you know, people scavenge.
以及搜刮的东西
Beer, bread, cut your head.
啤酒  面包  剪头
Cut your what?
剪什么
Barber.
理发师
Might be able to kill that thing on your head.
也许能拯救一下你头上那坨东西
We use a points system.
我们用的是工分系统
You're one of us now, not them.
你现在是我们中的一员了  和他们不一样
They eat shit, we eat good.
他们伙食糟糕  我们吃香喝辣
Write what you took or what they did,
写下你拿了什么  或者让他们做了什么
how much it was worth, sign your name.
然后写上对应的分数  再签个名
That's it.
就这么简单
Must be your lucky day, haircut.
今天一定是你的幸运日  长毛
Are these homemade?
这些是自家做的吗
Yeah.
是的
That's some good DIY stuff there.
真是不错的手工腌菜
No -- no, thank you.
不...不用了  谢谢
You want something...
你想要什么
you take it, haircut.
就拿什么  长毛
We'll send Simon over to take a peak,
我们让西蒙过去看一眼
sort of good-cop this thing first,
先来软的
see how far we get.
看看有什么效果
There he is.
他来了
Man of the hour!
全场焦点
Come on over here, big fella.
过来  大块头
Don't be rude, asshole.
别这么没礼貌  混蛋
Say hello.
说"你好"啊
H-h-hello.
你...好
You got a name, asshole?
你有名字吗  混蛋
Eugene.
尤金
Now us.
轮到我们了
Who are you?
你是谁
I'm Negan.
我是尼根
Well, Eugene...
尤金...
I know you remember Lucille.
我知道你还记得露西尔
Now, you see this right here?
你看见这里这个东西了吗
You might have to get real close.
你可能得靠近点仔细看看
That, my friend, is the bullet you made.
我的朋友  那是你造的子弹
Now, under normal circumstances,
在正常情况下
I'd be showing you that real close over and over again.
我会一遍又一遍地让你亲密接触它
But, Eugene, see,
但是  尤金  你瞧
all I really want to know is if you are a smarty-pants.
我只想知道你是不是个机灵鬼
You know things?
你懂的很多吗
Answer the question.
回答我
I -- I am, indeed, a smarty-pants.
我...我确实挺机灵的
I...taught myself to cast bullets.
我...自学了造子弹
I...found a --
我...找到了一个...
found a machine shop
找到了一个机械车间
with the necessary...
那里有必需的...
I-I read a lot, and, um...
我读了很多书...
although my --
尽管我...
Even though my memory is not considered eidetic,
尽管我做不到过目不忘
I don't skim and I don't scrimp.
但我也不会走马观花
If knowledge is dropped,
假如书上有什么知识
I do, indeed, pick it up.
我就会学会
Oh, you really are just some asshole.
你真的只是个混蛋而已
N-no. I'm not.
不  我不是
I have PHDs in biochemistry,
我有好几个生物化学
as well as immunology and microbiology,
以及免疫学与微生物学博士学位
and I've completed my doctorate, which makes me a doctor.
我完成了博士学业  是货真价实的博士
Prior to the collapse,
S05E01中尤金曾撒过同样的谎
I was part of a 10-person team at the human genome project,
我是人类基因组计划十人小组的成员
working under Dr. T. Brooks Ellis
受布鲁克斯・埃利斯博士领导
to weaponize diseases to fight weaponized diseases.
研制对抗病毒武器的病毒武器
Fire with, uh... You know...fire.
以毒...攻毒
Well, see, interdepartmental drinks were --
不同部门间喝过酒...
All right, Dr. Smarty-pants.
好吧  机灵鬼博士
You ought to be able to crack this without breaking a sweat.
你应该能不费吹灰之力解决这事
You see, I have a lot of free labor here at the fence,
你看  围栏边我有很多免费劳工
living dead pricks that help keep the riffraff out.
活死人可以防止其他杂碎进来
Problem is, they don't keep. They fall apart.
问题是它们站不住  总会散架
Like that poor sack of...
就像那摊可怜的
pile of shit there.
狗屎玩意
So, Dr. Smarty-Pants,
所以  机灵鬼博士
How do we keep them on their feet?
怎么才能让它们站住
You, um...
你们
smelt on the regs, correct?
经常冶炼  对吗
I saw that among the legacy equipment on the floor that
我看到一堆遗留设备当中
- you possess an operational smelter.  - And?
-有可运作的熔炉  -是又怎样
You already possess the means to resolve your issue.
你们已经掌握了解决问题的办法
Step one, melt down scrap metal.
第一步  熔化金属废料
Step two, pour it over the compromised walker
第二步  铁链拴住行尸
as they are in contact with the chain link.
把金属液浇到它们身上
The liquid metal will harden...
液态金属会变硬
Both maintaining bodily integrity for the walker
既可以保持行尸身体完整
as well as affixing them to the fence.
又可以把它们粘在围栏上
Bonus points for covering their head
更棒的是遮盖了它们的头部
and protecting them from head trauma from hostiles and calamities.
防止敌人攻击或意外导致脑袋碎裂
God damn!
靠
If that ain't the coolest thing I've ever heard in my life!
这是我这辈子听过的最酷的主意
Not only is that practical, it is just bad-ass!
不但可行  而且霸气
Look at you, Dr. Smarty-pants.
看看你  机灵鬼博士
Did Rick have you doing this kind of valuable stuff for him?
瑞克有没有让你替他做这些有意义的事
His loss, our gain.
他亏了  我们赚了
I feel like I need to give you some kind of signing bonus here.
我觉得应该给你签约奖金
Uh, w-well, I wa-- I was gifted these pickles.
我已经得到了腌黄瓜
No.
不
As a token of my gratitude,
作为对你的答谢
I'm gonna send you over a few of my wives
我要送我的老婆们
to your apartment tonight, show you a good time.
到你房间去  让你乐一乐
Now, I don't think I have to worry about this.
现在我不用担心这事了
But who knows how truly smart you are?
但谁又知道你到底有多聪明呢
No sex.
不准上床
That is a grave no-no.
那是禁区
However, you can have a little dinner,
但你可以吃顿惬意的晚餐
some drinks, share a few laughs.
喝喝小酒  乐呵乐呵
There is nothing like beautiful women that smell good
没什么比漂亮妞的体香
to make you feel human again.
更让你觉得自己又像个人了
I wouldn't know anything about that.
这方面我完全不了解
D-d-did you say "Wives", meaning plural?
你刚才说"老婆们"  是指有很多吗
Hell yes, I did.
正是
What does Dr. Smarty-pants say
机灵鬼博士要对
to his new bestest friend in the whole wide world?
他在世界上最好的新朋友说什么吗
What does he say?
要说什么吗
Thank you.
谢谢
Fully, completely...
非常地  完全地
Sincerely, seriously...Thank you.
诚心地  认真地感谢你
Okay.
好吧
Why don't you go have some fun?
去找点乐子吧
What the hell am I even looking at?
这是什么鬼东西
The insect-like creature is called Yar.
类似小虫子的生物叫亚尔
It is attempting to exact revenge
它们试图报复
upon the evil Qotile for the destruction of Razak IV.
恶魔昆塔  因为它摧毁了拉扎克四
Maybe you should take it easy, Amber.
也许你该放松点  安珀
Maybe I shouldn't, Frankie.
也许我不应该  弗兰基
Uh, we could play something else.
我们可以玩点别的
Warlords?
战神
It's four-player and quite the hoot.
可以四个人玩  很有趣
Whatever you want.
你想玩什么都行
This is your night.
今晚为你服务
Do you want a massage?
想来个按摩吗
Negan loves them.
尼根很喜欢
And I was a licensed therapist.
我是认证按摩师
You know, before.
以前是
While I appreciate the gesture
感谢你的好意
and your commitment to your assigned objective,
还有你对指定对象的认真精神
I am fully aware that none of you ladies are here this evening
我非常清楚今晚你们没有一位是
of your own volition.
出于自愿来的
Video games are all about me showing all of you a fun time.
电子游戏是我唯一可以展示给你们的乐子
Would you care for more microwave popcorn?
还想再吃点微波炉爆米花吗
Hey, just because this was Negan's idea
虽然这是尼根的主意
doesn't mean that we don't want to be here.
但不意味着我们不愿意来
I'd be down with just having an intelligent conversation.
只要有理性谈话  我就愿意来
Well, I suppose a conversation would be acceptable
我想在目前的情况下
under the current circumstance.
谈话是可以接受的
What would you like to talk about?
你们想谈什么
Uh, how about the human genome project?
人类基因组计划怎么样
I could talk about that shit all night.
我可以聊一整晚这玩意
In truth...
说实话
The bulk of my work for the HGP
我在人类基因组计划中的主要工作
fell under the auspices of the black box program,
属于黑盒子项目的一部分
of which I am not at liberty to discuss.
而我无权谈论此事
In all likelihood, even if I could,
就算我可以
it'd probably escape your comprehension.
你们也很可能无法理解
Did he just insult us, Tanya?
他刚侮辱了我们吗  塔尼娅
It was not a dis.
这不是侮辱
It was simply a statement of fact.
仅仅是陈述事实
My intelligence has been objectively measured.
我的智商经历过客观测量
I am fully a man apart.
我是个鹤立鸡群的人
So, what, are you, like, one of those guys who can make a bomb
那你就是那种能用漂白剂
out of bleach and a toothpick or something?
和牙签什么的做炸弹的人咯
Of course not.
当然不是
That would at least require dry yeast, hydrogen peroxide,
那至少需要干酵母  过氧化氢
and a small amount of liquid dish soap,
少量洗洁精
maybe some, you know, bathroom or drain cleaner,
也许还要一些洁厕灵或者通渠剂
some balloons or something like that,
一些气球之类的
few other common household sundries.
再加一些常见的生活用品
Seriously?
真的吗
Serious as sepsis.
千真万确
So stupid.
真蠢
I'm hoping to illustrate the opposite.
我希望这能展现我的聪明
Just slaves?
只是奴隶吗
Excuse me?
你说什么
Whatever.
随便了
Dr. Eugene, did you just make helium out of toilet stuff?
尤金博士  你刚用厕所里的东西制造了氦气吗
Hydrogen.
是氢气
It's cool, Keno.
没事  基诺
We're good.
我们没事
Relax.
放松
You're one of us.
你是我们中的一员了
I should disclose in advance
我应该提前说明
I may have oversold this one by classifying it as a bomb.
我将其归类为炸弹也许是有点说大话
As the hydrogen peroxide decomposes,
过氧化氢分解时
the reaction will release energy in the form of heat.
这一反应会以放热的形式释放能量
Dr. Eugene, can you please just show us some good shit?
尤金博士  你能给我们看点精彩的吗
I'm gonna light this candle.
我要点燃这根蜡烛
- Cool! - Finally.
-真酷  -终于
No, I mean, I'm gonna light this candle.
不  我是说  我要点燃这根蜡烛
Oh, no.
不
Yay!
耶
Yeah!
好棒
Honey?
亲爱的
D -- we always said that if we got separated,
D  我们总是说如果我们分开了
I should come back here and wait for you.
我应该回到这里等你
You'd show up with beer and pretzels.
你会带着啤酒和椒盐脆饼出现
You remember that?
记得吗
I know.
我知道
You probably don't.
你也许不记得了
You always said that when we started dating,
你总说我们开始约会时
you forgot to tell me you had a shitty memory.
你忘记告诉我你记性很差了
You used to get so frustrated by it...
你以前会因此很沮丧
knowing you wouldn't remember those good days...
知道你不会记得那些好时光
those special days.
特别的日子
I felt bad for you.
我为你感到难过
I remember you said
我记得你说过
there was so much you wanted to hold on to,
你有许多想记住的事
and then it'd be gone.
但你就这样忘了
But you're lucky you don't remember things, D.
但你很幸运你记性不好  D
I wish I could wait for you now.
真希望我现在能等你
But I don't know if you'd come with me
但我不知道你会跟我走
Or if you'd take me back there
还是带我回去
Or you'd kill me.
还是杀了我
You didn't want to live in that world,
你不想活在那个世界里
and I made you.
是我逼你的
I did what I did because I didn't want you to die.
我那样做是因为我不想让你死
But now you've killed,
但现在你杀人了
and you've become everything you didn't want to be,
成为了你不想成为的人
And it's my fault.
这是我的错
You were better than me.
你比我更好
Most people are.
大部分人都是
I let Daryl go
我放达里尔走
Because he reminded you of who you used to be.
因为他让你想起了以前的自己
And I wanted to let you forget.
而我想让你忘掉
I don't think I'm gonna make it out here,
我不觉得自己能在外面活下去
but you're wrong.
但你错了
Being there isn't better than being dead.
在那里并不比死了更好
It's worse.
而是更糟
I hope you realize that,
我希望你能明白
and I hope you get away.
希望你能离开那
I hope you remember the good days,
我希望你记得那些美好的时光
even just one of them, but...
哪怕只记得一点  但是...
I don't think you will.
我不认为你会想起来
I don't think you'll ever read this.
你也许根本不会读到这封信
I loved who you were.
我爱以前的你
I'm sorry I made you into who you are.
很抱歉  我让你变成了现在这样
Goodbye.
再见
Honey.
亲爱的
We can hear the Yars and the Qotile, Eugene.
我们听到你在玩亚尔和昆塔了  尤金
I was given to understand that last night's shinny
在我的理解里  昨晚的事情
was supposed to be a singular incident.
应该是单一偶发事件
He didn't send us.
不是他叫我们来的
We need your help.
我们需要你的帮助
You saw Amber last night.
昨晚你看到安珀的样子了
She just drinks and cries.
喝了哭  哭了喝
She didn't want this.
她不想做这个
We signed up for it.
我们是自愿的
It's better for us.
对我们来说更好
She had to.
她是被迫的
Her mom needed meds.
她妈妈需要药
She can't work.
她又不能干活
Amber thought...
安珀本以为
that she could live with it.
她可以忍受
She can't.
她做不到
She asked us to help her end it.
她求我们帮她结束这一切
You aren't afforded any...
你们没有什么
mental-health services?
心理健康辅导可做吗
No.
没有
- Are you serious? - I mean, there's a licensed masseuse here.
-你是认真的吗  -你们有认证女按摩师
Uh, odds being what they are --
按概率来说  应该...
There's no one like that here.
没有那样的人
So this...is it.
只能这样了
She just wants to take something.
她只是想吃点什么
She wants to go to sleep and not wake up.
睡过去  再不醒过来
That would be wildly irresponsible.
那样非常不负责任
She dies at night, in her sleep,
她在睡梦中死去
she turns while everyone is asleep...
变成行尸的时候  其他人都在睡觉
We'll handle that part.
我们负责处理那部分
We were hoping that you could make something for her,
我们希望你能帮她做点什么
'cause we know that you can make things.
因为我们知道你会做东西
Look, I know that this is crazy and you barely know us...
我知道这很疯狂  你也不怎么了解我们
But we can tell that you are a good man.
但是我们知道你是个好人
There aren't many of those left.
现在好人不多了
Truth of the matter is, I'm not good.
事实上  我不是好人
I'm not lawful, neutral, or chaotic --
我不守序  不中立  不叛逆
None of the above.
以上都不是
Are you saying you can't do it?
你是说你不会做是吗
Lack of ability is not the problem here.
并不是能力缺失的问题
I could jerry-rig a lethal toxin
我可以用现有的材料
with the assets at hand here.
随意提取出某种致命毒素
- No problemo. I have the -- - Then help us.
-没问题  我是...  -那就帮帮我们
A pill, a shot, whatever.
一片药  一小杯药水  都可以
We need two of them.
我们需要两份
'cause we don't know when we could get our chance.
因为我们不知道什么时候才有机会
She's gonna do it, with or without us.
无论我们帮不帮她  她都要寻死的
She'll suffer, and maybe someone else will get hurt.
她会很痛苦  或者导致其他人受伤
You are good, Eugene.
你是好人  尤金
You have to be.
你一定要是
How much does she weigh?
她有多重
Don't know. Maybe...120.
不知道  一百二吧
Why?
怎么了
If you could get me her exact weight,
如果你们能告诉我她的准确体重
I could guarantee a semi-precise t.O. Pain-free d.
我可以保证做出半精加工无痛毒药
A.S.A.P.
尽快做出
Best I can do for now.
目前只能这样了
Come back later.
晚点再来吧
We're playing poker with some guys.
我们几个人玩扑克
Try to hook you up.
试着帮你牵线
You kidding? Can't play poker.
你在开玩笑吗  玩不了扑克了
I got to be out diggin' postholes
明天早上天一亮
at the crack of dawn tomorrow.
我就得出去挖坑
I would like a single blister pack
我需要一板铝塑包装的
of your most extra-strength cold capsule.
最强效的感冒胶囊
The line's a line!
队是用来排的
What, they not have them where you come from?
怎么  你老家都不排队吗
You don't know how they work?
你不知道怎么排吗
No, I am familiar --
不  我熟悉...
Get in it, prick.
后面排着去  混蛋
What is your number?
你的编号是多少
What's yours?
你的呢
All right, number 16.
好吧  16号
My name is Dr. Eugene Porter.
我是尤金・波特博士
I've recently been appointed
我最近被授予了
to the newly created post of chief engineer of this facility.
这里新设立的首席工程师之职
I report directly to Negan,
我直属尼根管理
which means you report directly to my ass.
这意味着你直属我管理
The cold capsules, now.
我要感冒胶囊  快点
I didn't know.
我不知道
We just -- we get so many new faces, I didn't...
只是  来的新人很多...
I want this, too.
这个我也要
And this.
还有这个
I don't even know what you call this.
我不知道你管这叫什么
I'm gonna call it a gremblygunk.
我要叫它小黏糊
Did you find her?
你找到她了吗
Where is she?
她在哪
I killed her.
我杀了她
She ran away from me right into a mess of dead ones,
她逃向了一群行尸中
So, I, uh... Made it quick.
所以我...给了她痛快
It still hurts.
还是会痛
Feels better with a bandage.
有绷带好一些
I wasn't talking about that.
我不是说这个
I would tell you to just forget about her, but...
我本想告诉你忘了她  但是...
...I don't see anyone else doing that anytime soon,
考虑到她做的事情  我不觉得短时间内
considering what she did.
会有人这么做
Oh, we've all done things.
我们都做过一些事情
Yes, but before we got here,
是的  但在我们来这里之前
Before we understood...
在我们懂得之前
We were cowards about it.
我们像个懦夫
We don't -- we don't get to have big hearts.
我们...不能留有善良之心
Remember that.
记住这一点
Wh-what is this?
这是干什么
You'll find out.
你会知道的
You are gonna want to pay close attention to this.
你最好睁眼好好看着
no, no, no, no!
不
Why?
为什么
I didn't do anything.
我什么都没做
I found this little souvenir
我发现这个小纪念品
tucked away in your desk.
藏在你的桌子里
I-I-I don't know what that is.
我不知道那是什么
You...
你
left the door open and let my puppy out.
开门放走了我的宠物
You knew Sherry hated Daryl being here,
你知道雪莉不希望达里尔在这里
So you let him out for her, be the hero.
所以你为她放了他  趁机逞英雄
Then you could move in.
然后你就可以插一脚了
That...
你...
is some weaselly shit right there.
真够狡猾
But I didn't. She's the one who ran --
我没这么做  是她自己逃跑的...
Oh, she ran?
她逃跑
You know why she ran?!
你知道为什么她会逃吗
Because she knew I would blame her, which...
因为她知道我会怪她
I did.
确实如此
But, see, Sherry told Dwighty boy the whole story
但是雪莉在她被撕碎之前
right before she was torn apart.
告诉了小德整件事的经过
A super hot girl, horrifically killed
一个超级辣妹  因为你的
Because of your greedy, delusional,
痴心妄想和小鸡鸡
and tiny little prick.
被残忍杀死
It's not true. Dwight?
这不是真的  德怀特
He's lying about it.
他在撒谎
- I would never do that. - Why?
-我决不会这么做  -为什么
Why? Why would he do that?
为什么  为什么他要撒谎呢
Why would he intentionally try to hurt you?
为什么他要故意伤害你呢
Sherry's gone.
雪莉死了
And if he's lying...
如果他撒了谎
And she's out there, I will find her.
她还活着  我会找到她
And then I will burn the other side of his face off
然后我会烧了他另外半张脸
until he dies.
直到他死
So, what was he gonna get out of this?
他能从中得到什么好处呢
No.
不
You see, I know my Dwighty boy.
我了解我的小德
See, all he needed...
他需要的只是
was one more night in the hole,
在牢房里再被关一晚
get his head screwed on straight.
然后脑子就正常了
It worked before, and it worked now.
以前管用  现在也管用
Ain't that right, Dwight?
是不是啊  德怀特
Oh, yeah.
是的
oh, please.
求求你
No, please.
不  求求你
Oh, jesus, don't burn me.
天啊  不要烫我
Please!
求求你
No.
不
No, no, please!
不  求求你
Now you know I hate this shit.
你知道我讨厌这样做
Just tell me you did it and that you're sorry,
只用告诉我是你做的  你很抱歉
And I don't have to do this.
我就不用动手了
Yes.
是的
Yes, I did it -- all of it.
是我做的  都是我做的
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
抱歉  我很抱歉
Please...
求求你
I'm sorry.
抱歉
That's all you had to say.
这么说就行了
A good thing we got a spare Dr. Carson.
幸好我们还有个卡森医生
I trust you, Dwighty boy.
我相信你  小德
Never shoulda doubted you.
从来不该怀疑你
Sherry was one of my favorites.
雪莉是我最喜欢的女人之一
I'm sorry.
我很遗憾
I'm not.
我不
Ice-cold.
冷血
I love it.
我喜欢
Come.
进
Hello.
你好
Are you all right?
你还好吗
Better than that.
挺好的
You can call next, but it might be a while.
你可以下局玩  不过要等一会
Did you make the pills?
你做药了吗
I did.
做了
But you can't have them.
但不能给你们
Amber's counting on us.
安珀指望着我们呢
We told her that you were gonna help us,
我们跟她说你会帮助我们
- and she says that she -- - Pump your brakes, red.
-她说她...  -住嘴  红发
Do not insult my intelligence, Frankie.
别侮辱我的智商  弗兰基
Said pills aren't for Amber.
药不是给安珀的
Said pills are for Negan.
药是给尼根的
That's why you wanted two.
所以你要两份
Didn't he kill your friends?
他不是杀了你的朋友们吗
Several.
杀了好几个
But I imagine we killed about 30 or so of his.
但我们也杀了他的三十多个人
Turnabout and all that.
扯平了
Give us the pills, or we'll tell Negan about it.
给我们药  不然我们给尼根告状
We'll tell him that it was your idea to make them
我们会说做药是你的主意
and that you tried to get us to help.
你试图劝我们协助你
That would be a tactical error on your part.
那会是你的战术错误
They'll believe me over you
他会信我而不是你
for the same reason he believed Dwight over the doctor.
正如他信德怀特而不是医生一样
You're replaceable to him.
你对他来说是可取代的
I, on the other hand, am not.
另一方面  我则不是
You're a coward.
你是个懦夫
You're...a coward.
你是个...懦夫
That is a correct assessment.
这是正确的评价
May I come in?
我能进来吗
So, how you liking it here?
你喜欢这里吗
Are we doing right by Dr. Smarty-pants?
我们把机灵鬼博士招待得好吗
You know, Frankie and Tanya...
弗兰基和塔尼娅
Nothing but good things to say about you.
她们说的都是你的好话
It's all right.
没关系
I get it.
我明白
I know how hard it can be to accept change,
我知道接受改变
to get on the right team.
弃暗投明有多难
But I need you to understand something.
但是我需要你明白一些事
I do not make this invitation to everyone.
我不会随意邀请他人
And I sure as shit do not make it lightly.
我的邀请分量也很重
You do not need to be scared anymore.
你不用再害怕了
You don't need to be scared.
你不用害怕了
You just have to answer me one question.
只用回答我一个问题
And it's a big one.
这是个大问题
Who are --
你是...
I'm Negan.
我是尼根
I'm utterly, completely, stone-cold Negan.
我完完全全  彻头彻尾是尼根
I was Negan before I even met you.
遇见你之前我就是尼根了
I just needed to meet you properly to know.
遇见你之后  我才醒悟
I'm Negan.
我是尼根
Hey, be careful with that.
当心点
Hey, you want to get burned by molten metal?
你想被熔态金属烫到吗
'cause that's exactly how you get burned by molten metal.
因为那样做会被熔态金属烫到的
Regarding me clamping down --
关于我施压...
You on board?
你跟我们一伙吗
I am. Just like you.
是的  和你一样
Don't know if you recall my handle -- I don't.
-不知道你是否记得我名字  -不记得
Eugene.
尤金
You're Dwight.
你是德怀特
We are Negan.
我们都是尼根
Yeah.
是啊